Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Publications Collection, 1887-2005 RL.00741
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- International Publications Series (Restricted), 1914-2003 and undated, 22 boxes
  - Other Offices Publications, 1914-2003 and undated
    - Brazil
      - [ Jota Dabliu Te, undated (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV4)] (Box IO2)
      - [ JWT, undated: Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV4] (Box IO2)
      - JWT Brazil-1970, 1970 (Box IO2)
      - O Público e a Propaganda, 1967 (Box IO2)
    - Canada
      - Brief Profile of JWT New York, undated (Box IO3)
      - Canadian, 1955 (Box IO3)
      - Canadian Profile of JWT, 1972 (Box IO3)
      - Cream of Your Market, 1954 (Box IO3)
      - Institutional Food Market in Canada, 1956 (Box IO3)
      - JWT au Canada, 1976 (Box IO3)
      - J. Walter Thompson, 1981 (Box IO3)
      - [ Marketing In Crisis, 1994 (Removed to Other Offices Publications, Restricted Materials, box IO12)] (Box IO3)
      - Modern Advertising Agency Service, 1914 (Box IO3)
      - Outline for An Advertising Agency Analysis, 1951 (Box IO3)
      - Plain Talk on Research, 1955 (Box IO3)
      - Project Enterprise, 1975 (Box IO3)
      - What Has Happened to the Advertising Dollar?, 1958 (Box IO3)
    - Denmark
      - [ JWT, 1996 (Removed to Other Offices Publications, Restricted Materials, box IO12)] (Box IO3)
      - [ Naget om JWT før og nu, 1972 (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV4)] (Box IO3)
      - Passport to the North, 1986 (Box IO3)
    - Europe
      - Few Facts about J. Walter Thompson Company, 1985 (Box IO3)
      - James Webb Young Course, 1991
        - 1. Craft Skills Seminar (Box IO3)
        - 2. Business Skills Seminar (Box IO3)
        - 3. Multinational Client Services (Box IO3)
        - 5. Management Simulation (Box IO3)
      - JWT Europe, 1968 (Box IO3)
      - Managers Meeting, 1990 (Box IO3)
      - Map and Guide of European Cities, 1991 (Box IO3)
      - Media Information--Switzerland, 1968
        - Europe, 1970-1971 (Box IO3)
        - Switzerland, 1968 (Box IO3)
      - New Map for Europe, undated (Box IO3)
      - New Office Announcement, 1990 (Box IO3)
      - Professional Development Programme, 1985 (Box IO3)
      - [ Training and Professional Development in the European Region, 1995 (Removed to Other Offices Publications, Restricted Materials, box IO12)] (Box IO3)
    - Europe/Middle East/Africa
      - [ Benchmark, 2001 (Bound volume of advertisements, removed to Oversize Materials, box OV4)] (Box IO3)
      - [ Passion '03: JWT Europe, Middle East, Africa (Bound volume of advertisements, removed to Oversize Materials, box OV3)] (Box IO3)
    - France
      - [ Account Management Development Program, 1993 (Removed to Other Offices Publications, Restricted Materials, box IO12)] (Box IO4)
      - [ Aspects of Real, 1992 (Removed to Other Offices Publications, Restricted Materials, box IO12)] (Box IO4)
      - Devoirs de Vacances, 1984 (Box IO4)
      - Grassland Improvement Campaign for OEEC Countries, circa 1940 (Box IO4)
      - [ J. Walter Thompson, 1993 (Removed to Other Offices Publications, Restricted Materials, box IO12)] (Box IO4)
      - J. Walter Thompson Agence de Publicité, 1985 (Box IO4)
      - JWT 1973-1974, circa 1975 (Box IO4)
      - JWT en France, 1970 (Box IO4)
      - [ L'Equipe, 1995 (Removed to Other Offices Publications, Restricted Materials, box IO12)] (Box IO4)
      - La Lettre d'Information Media, 1984 (Box IO4)
      - [ Ouvre, 1995 (Removed to Other Offices Publications, Restricted Materials, box IO12)] (Box IO4)
      - Strategic Concept of Consumer Involvement: It's Importance Today, undated (Box IO4)
      - Women in the 90's--A New Age in Marketing to Women, undated (Box IO4)
    - Germany
      - Corporate Communications, 1982 (Box IO4)
      - Der Planungsberater, 1981, 1982, 1985, 3 folders (Box IO4)
      - Die Dynamik des Wertewandels in Unserer Gesellschaft, 1984 (Box IO4)
      - Ein Portrait, 1980 (Box IO4)
      - Eine Technik zum Produzieren von Ideen, 1983 (Box IO4)
      - European Common Market, 1959 (Box IO4)
      - Geschäftsbericht, 1974 (Box IO4)
      - Jahresbericht, 1975 (Box IO4)
      - Jahresring 1973, 1973 (Box IO4)
      - JWT Frankfurt, circa 1963, 1971, 1972, 3 folders (Box IO4)
      - JWT in Frankfurt, 1970 (Box IO4)
      - [ Media Information, 1993 (Removed to Other Offices Publications, Restricted Materials, box IO12)] (Box IO4)
      - Portrait, 1983 (Box IO4)
      - [ Portrait, 1984 (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV4)] (Box IO4)
      - Willkommen bei J. Walter Thompson, undated (Box IO4)
    - Greece
      - JWT in Greece, 1975 (Box IO5)
    - Hong Kong
      - Happy Birthday Cards, undated (Box IO5)
      - J. Walter Thompson, undated (Box IO5)
      - [ Marketwise, 2000 (Removed to Other Offices Publications, Restricted Materials, box IO12)] (Box IO5)
    - India
      - Advertisment Films in Movie Houses, 1955 (Box IO5)
      - Annual Report, 1970-1974, 1977, 1978, 1982, 1985, 9 folders (Box IO5)
      - Hindustan Thompson Associates Ltd., circa 1967 (Box IO5)
      - Hindustan Thompson List of Clients, 1983 (Box IO5)
      - HTA Our People, 1980 (Box IO5)
      - HTA Today, 1980 (Box IO5)
      - Reports and Accounts, 1969 (Box IO5)
      - Rural Hyderabad, circa 1948 (Box IO5)
      - Salute to the Stars, 1990 (Box IO5)
      - Thompson Consumer Index of Markets, 1960, 1963, 2 folders (Box IO5)
      - Thompson Rural Market Index, 1972 (Box IO5)
    - Indonesia
      - P.T. Thomertwal Advertising, undated (Box IO6)
    - Ireland
      - DDFH&B, undated (Box IO6)
    - Italy
      - Annual Report J.W.T. Italia, 1979, 1981, 1983, 1984, 4 folders (Box IO6)
      - Bravi & Buoni, 1994 (collection of office artwork) (Box IO6)
      - Crisi Nell'Attività di Marca, 1982 (Box IO6)
      - Il Mercato U.S.A. per le Merci Italiane, 1950 (Box IO6)
      - J. Walter Thompson (Italia) S.P.A., circa 1960 (Box IO6)
      - [ JWT Business Communications, circa 1994 (Removed to Other Offices Publications, Restricted Materials, box IO12)] (Box IO6)
      - JWT Italy, circa 1970 (Box IO7)
      - Lo Sviluppo di Nuove Marche, 1982 (Box IO7)
      - Rapporto Annuale, 1981, 1983, 2 folders (Box IO7)
      - Studio Sull'Immagine delle Reti Televisive, 1984 (Box IO7)
      - [ Who's Who, undated (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV5)] (Box IO7)
    - Japan
      - [ JWT Guide to Research Japan Version, 1992 (Removed to Other Offices Publications, Restricted Materials, box IO12 (Box IO7)
      - [ JWT Media Person's Handbook Japan Version, 1992 (Removed to Other Offices Publications, Restricted materials, box IO12)] (Box IO7)
      - Symposium in Commemoration of the 25th Anniversary of JWT Japan, 1981 (Box IO7)
      - Thompson Way, undated (Box IO7)
    - Korea
      - Annual Report, 1984 (Box IO7)
    - Mexico
      - Estudio de Radio y Televisión, 1960 (Box IO7)
      - Market Data, 1957 (Box IO7)
      - Mexican Market, 1959, 1963, 2 folders (Box IO7)
      - [ Passion 03: JWT Latinoamerica, 2003 (Bound volume of advertisements, removed to Oversize Materials, box OV5)] (Box IO7)
      - Population Study, 1957 (Box IO7)
      - Walter Thompson de Mexico S.A., 1952 (Box IO7)
      - WTM en Mexico, 1970, 2 folders (Box IO7)
    - Netherlands
      - Classification of the Content of the Advertising Message, undated (Box IO8)
      - De Ideeën liggen op Straat, 1983 (Box IO8)
      - Een Grootgrutter op Net Oorlogspad, 1983 (Box IO8)
      - Food Retailing in the Netherlands, 1964 (Box IO8)
      - JWT NIEUW, circa 1983 (Box IO8)
      - [ PPGH/JWT Business Communications, circa 1992 (Removed to Other Offices Publications, Restricted Materials, box IO12)] (Box IO8)
      - PPGH/JWT in 15 Characteristics, 1989 (Box IO8)
      - PPGH/JWT Tien Jaar Merkenbeleid, 1991 (Box IO8)
      - PPGH/Moussault Werke, 1987 (Box IO8)
      - Retail-Unit, circa 1973 (Box IO8)
      - Role of a New Brand Venture Group Within JWT Amsterdam, circa 1975 (Box IO8)
    - New Zealand
      - JWT Opportunities in New Zealand, 1971 (Box IO8)
    - Peru
      - Conozca Thompson, circa 1992 (Box IO8)
      - JWT Marzo 1981, 1981 (Box IO8)
      - JWT Peru, circa 1978 (Box IO8)
      - Perfil del Mercado Peruano, 1982-1983, 2 folders (Box IO8)
      - Peruvian Market Profile, 1972 (Box IO8)
      - Una Téchnica para Producir Ideas, undated (Box IO8)
    - Philippines
      - [ J. Walter Thompson, 1982 (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV5)] (Box IO8)
      - J. Walter Thompson Philippines 1947-1982, undated (Box IO8)
      - JWT, circa 1979 (Box IO9)
      - JWT At Forty, undated (Box IO9)
      - Philippine Market, 1961, 1967, 4 folders (Box IO9)
    - Portugal
      - Portuguese Grafitti, undated (Box IO9)
    - South Africa
      - 1975 Communications Plan, 1975 (Box IO9)
      - African Market Division: A Statisitical Overview, 1974 (Box IO9)
      - Biography of Roland T. Wentzel, 1993 (Box IO9)
      - Entertaining with Wines of the Cape, 1962 (Box IO9)
      - Handbook on Wine for Retail Licensees, 1956 (Box IO9)
      - I-Group Network Text, 1975 (Box IO9)
      - J. Walter Thompson, undated (Box IO9)
      - JWT Audit of Agency Performance, 1971 (Box IO9)
      - JWT Circle: A Quarterly Review for the Staff of JWT Southern Africa, 1972 (Box IO9)
      - Lining Up for Launch Day, 1974 (Box IO9)
      - Markets to the North, 1954 (Box IO10)
        - General, 1954 (Box IO10)
        - Angola, 1956 (Box IO10)
        - Belgian Congo, 1956 (Box IO10)
        - British East Africa, 1956, 1957, 2 folders (Box IO10)
        - Mozambique or Portuguese East Africa, 1956 (Box IO10)
        - Rhodesia and Nyasaland, 1956 (Box IO10)
        - South West Africa, 1956 (Box IO10)
      - Overview, 1971 (Box IO10)
      - South African Clients, 1969 (Box IO10)
      - Southern African Intelligence: General Market Report No. 47, 1965 (Box IO10)
      - Statistical Overview of the South African Market, 1969, 1970, 2 folders (Box IO10)
      - Theoretical Case for Professionalism (part 1 and 2), circa 1969 (Box IO10)
    - Spain
      - Allegro Vivace: The History of Champagne, Cava and the Sparkling Wines of the World, 1988 (Box IO10)
      - Annual Report, 1977-1980, 3 folders (Box IO10)
      - Como Opera la Publicidad? undated (Box IO10)
      - Desarollo Practico de una Téoria de los Anunciós, 1977 (Box IO10)
      - Donde Comer en Madrid en Agosto, 1992 (Box IO10)
      - El Mercado y Nuestros Anuncios, 1984 (Box IO10)
      - [ Esto No Es Un Cuchillo de Palo, 1991 (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV5)] (Box IO10)
      - Glosario Publicitano Español-Ingles, Ingles-Español, undated (Box IO10)
      - Guiá para la realización de una Spot Publicitano, undated (Box IO10)
      - Historia Incompleta, undated (Box IO10)
      - [ J. Walter Thompson, 1996 (Removed to Other Offices Publications, Restricted Materials, box IO12)] (Box IO10)
      - JWT España de 1927-1936, 1978 (Box IO10)
      - La Inversion Publicitaria en España, 1981-1985, Folders 1-2 of 5 (Box IO10)
      - La Inversion Publicitaria en España, 1981-1985 (continued), Folders 3-5 of 4 (Box IO11)
      - La Investigación Publicitaria en la Agencia, 1977 (Box IO11)
      - Mil Novecientos setenta y nueve, 1977, 1978, 2 folders (Box IO11)
      - Mis Ajás Preferidos sobre Promoción de Ventas, 1976 (Box IO11)
      - No Esán Todos Los Que Son, Pero Si Son Todos Los Que Están, 1978 (Box IO11)
      - Publicidad en 1979, 1979 (Box IO11)
    - Sweden
      - [ Resultattavlor, 1984 (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV5)] (Box IO11)
    - Uruguay
      - Corporación/Thompson, circa 1992 (Box IO11)
  - Other Offices Publications, Restricted Materials (Closed to non-JWT users), 1992-2000
    - Argentina (Box IO12)
      - Manual Operativa para Cuentas, 1994, 2 folders (Box IO12)
    - Australia
      - Dreaming, 1993 (Box IO12)
    - Canada
      - Marketing in Crisis, 1994 (Box IO12)
    - Europe
      - Training and Professional Development in the Eurpoean Region, 1995 (Box IO12)
    - France
      - Account Management Development Program, 1993 (Box IO12)
      - Aspects of Real, 1992 (Box IO12)
      - J. Walter Thompson, 1993 (Box IO12)
      - L'Equipe, 1995 (Box IO12)
      - Ouvre, 1995 (Box IO12)
    - Germany
      - Media Information, 1993 (Box IO12)
    - Hong Kong
      - Marketwise, 2000 (Box IO12)
    - Italy
      - JWT Business Communications, circa 1994 (Box IO12)
    - Japan
      - JWT Guide to Research Japan Version, 1992 (Box IO12)
      - JWT Media Person's Handbook Japan Version, 1992 (Box IO12)
    - Netherlands
      - PPGH/JWT Business Communications, circa 1992 (Box IO12)
    - Spain
      - J. Walter Thompson, 1996 (Box IO12)
- Subsidiaries and Related Firms Publications Series (Restricted), 1950-2002 and undated, 6 boxes
  Publications produced by JWT subsidiaries, partners and affiliated firms. Arranged alphabetically by corporate name and then by publication title. Restricted materials are collocated and at the end of the listings of corporate entities.
  Restriction note: Materials published by JWT or its subsidiaries that are less than fifteen years old, other than advertisements, are closed to non-JWT users. Materials published by non-JWT companies that are less than fifteen years old are open to researchers. Individual boxes are so marked. Where items have been removed and relocated to Restricted Materials, that item has been replaced by a dummy folder indicated by a title in brackets.
  - A.C. Nielsen Company GMBH (Frankfurt, Germany), 1980
    - Werbelöcher: Muß das sein?, 1980 (Box SR1)
  - Advertising Creative Circle (London, UK), 1953
    - Artist in Advertising, 1953 (Box SR1)
  - Advertising Research Foundation
    - Research Audit of 1978 TGI, 1978 (Box SR1)
    - Research Audit Report of SMRB 1985 Study of Media and Markets, 1985 (Box SR1)
  - American Institute of Consumer Studies (Newton Square, Penn.), 2002
    - Survey of American Consumers, 2002 (Box SR1)
  - Axiom Market Research Bureau (New York, N.Y.), 1972-1977
    - Ballad of Reggie Research and TGI, 1972 (Box SR1)
    - Comparison of Methods, 1973 (Box SR1)
    - Guide to Consumer Self-Cencept, 1973 (Box SR1)
    - Measuring the Audience of Magazines, 1972 (Box SR1)
    - Measuring Self-Concept, 1972 (Box SR1)
    - Sample Product and Brand Tables, 1973 (Box SR1)
    - Target Group Index Plan, 1972-1978 (Box SR1)
    - Target Teen Index, 1976 (Box SR1)
    - Technical Plan, 1975 (Box SR1)
    - Trends in Magazine Audiences, 1975 (Box SR1)
  - British Market Research Bureau (London, U.K.), 1950-1974 and undated
    - About BMRB, undated (Box SR2)
    - ACCESS, undated (Box SR2)
    - Access: The BMRB Omnibus Study, undated (Box SR2)
    - Approach to Measuring Advertising Effectiveness, 1962 (Box SR2)
    - Brand Personality, 1968 (Box SR2)
    - Britain: Its Markets and Media, 1965 (Box SR2)
    - British Market Research Bureau, 1970, 1974, 2 folders (Box SR2)
    - Career in Market Research, 1964 (Box SR2)
    - Creative Workshop, undated (Box SR2)
    - Creative Workshop: Butter, 1965 (Box SR2)
    - Education, Social Class, and Reading of Newspapers and Magazines, 1966 (Box SR2)
    - Food and Cooking in England, 1964 (Box SR2)
    - Industrial Marketing Research at BMRB, undated (Box SR2)
    - Market Research in Europe, 1972 (Box SR2)
    - Problem Solvers, undated (Box SR2)
    - Psychological Laboratory, undated (Box SR2)
    - Retail Audit: Principles and Practice, 1960 (Box SR2)
    - Retail Display and Packaging, undated (Box SR2)
    - Round the Woman, 1960 (Box SR2)
    - Sampling Shops, 1960 (Box SR2)
    - Self-Service in Great Britain, 1950 (Box SR2)
    - Sixty-Four Problems, undated (Box SR2)
    - Social Class Definitions in Market Research: Objectives and Practice, 1963 (Box SR2)
    - Social Class in Sample Surveys, 1954 (Box SR2)
    - Statistical Accuracy of the IPA NRS Results, circa 1965 (Box SR2)
    - Target Group Index, 1970 (Box SR2)
    - Target Panel, 1969 (Box SR2)
    - Western Europe, 1954, 1956-1957, 3 folders (Box SR3)
  - Brouillard Communications (New York, N.Y.), 1975-1986 and undated
    - Brouillard Communications, undated (Box SR3)
    - Brouillard in Brief, 1984, 1986, 2 folders (Box SR3)
    - Corporate Need to Communicate, 1975 (Box SR3)
    - How to Win in the Public Eye, undated (Box SR3)
    - Importance of Corporate Advertising for Communication with the U.S. Capital Market, undated (Box SR3)
    - What's New from the Corporate Point of View, 1988 (Box SR3)
  - Communispond, Inc., 1977
    - Communispond, Inc., circa 1977 (Box SR3)
  - Consultancy Group, 1976
    - Consultancy Group, circa 1976 (Box SR3)
  - Contract Advertising (India) Limited (Bombay), 1994-1995
    - [ Up Front, vol. 3, 1995 (Removed to Subsidiaries and Related Firms, Restricted Materials, box SR6)] (Box SR3)
    - [ Upbeat, 1994 (Removed to Subsidiaries and Related Firms, Restricted Materials, box SR6)] (Box SR3)
  - Deltakos (New York, N.Y.), 1973-1977
    - Darvon Pricing Survey, 1977 (Box SR4)
    - Preliminary Report on the Present Pharmaceutical Situation and the Areas of Opportunity for Deltakos (Belgium), 1973 (Box SR4)
    - Proposal for a Series of Focus Groups on Birth Control Methods, 1976 (Box SR4)
  - Diogenes Market Research, Inc (New York, N.Y.), 1978
    - Introducing Diogenes, circa 1978 (Box SR4)
  - Duke University, 1988, 1999
    - J. Walter Thompson Co. Archives, 1988, 1999 (Box SR4)
  - EA International/Euro Advertising (Paris, France), 1979-1982
    - [ EA Euro-Lyon, 1979 (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV6)] (Box SR4)
    - EA International, 1982 (Box SR4)
    - [ Press Information, 1980 (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV6)] (Box SR4)
  - Editora Referência, Ltda. (São Paulo, Brazil), 1979-1989
    - Propaganda, 1973-1989, 2 folders (Box SR4)
  - European Market Research Bureau (EMRB), 1972-1973
    - Market Research in Europe, 1972 (Box SR4)
    - Market Research on a European Basis, 1973 (Box SR4)
    - Motor Racing Sponsorship: A Proposal for a Three-Country Survey, 1973 (Box SR4)
  - Hill & Knowlton (New York, N.Y.), 1980-1987
    - Annual Review, 1981-1984, 4 folders (Box SR4)
    - Hill & Knowlton, 1980, 1986, 1987, 3 folders (Box SR4)
    - Newsletter, 1983 July (Box SR4)
    - Platform, 1986-1987 (Box SR4)
    - Public Issues, Public Policy Group, 1980 (Box SR4)
    - Who We Are, circa 1981 (Box SR4)
  - Huhtamäki Oy (Helsinki, Finland), 1986
    - Huhtamäki 1985, 1986 (Box SR4)
  - Innovative Information Techniques, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1992
    - Working Smarter Through Better Time Management, 1992 (Box SR4)
  - JWT Direct (Chicago, Ill.), 1986
    - J. Walter Thompson Direct, 1986 (Box SR4)
  - JWT Specialized Communications (Dallas, Tex.), 1996-2000
    - [ Escape the Mundane, 2000 (Removed to Subsidiaries and Related Firms, Restricted Materials, box SR6)] (Box SR4)
    - [ JWT Specialized Communications, circa 1996 (Removed to Subsidiaries and Related Firms, Restricted Materials, box SR6)] (Box SR4)
  - JWT Works (Dallas, Tex.), 2000
    - [ Working Wire, 2000 (Removed to Subsidiaries and Related Firms, Restricted Materials, box SR6)] (Box SR4)
  - JWT Worldwide (New York, N.Y.), 1995 and undated
    - [ Cold Hard Facts, 1995 and undated (Removed to Subsidiaries and Related Firms, Restricted Materials, box SR6)], 2 folders (Box SR4)
  - Landsdowne Advertising (New York, N.Y.), 1975-1980s
    - [ Landsdowne, 1979 (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV6)] (Box SR5)
    - Landsdowne, circa 1980s (Box SR5)
    - [ Landsdowne Marketing Limited, 1975 (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV6)] (Box SR5)
  - Lexington International (London, U.K.), 1978
    - Lexington International, circa 1978 (Box SR5)
  - Lord, Geller, Federico, Einstein (New York, N.Y.), 1981-1985
    - [ LGFE, 1981, 1984-1985, (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV7)], 3 folders (Box SR5)
  - Market Research Bureau International--MRBI (London, U.K.), 1983
    - MRB International, 1983 (Box SR5)
  - McGraw-Hill Research (New York, N.Y.), 1985
    - Laboratory of Advertising Performance, 1985, 3 folders (Box SR5)
  - Mediamark Research (New York, N.Y.), 2002
    - Magazine Audience Estimates, 2002 (Box SR5)
  - Mindshare (New York, N.Y.), 1999 and undated
    - [ Making the Partnership Work, 1999 (Removed to Subsidiaries and Related Firms, Restricted Materials, box SR6)] (Box SR5)
    - [ Some Things We Learned About Launching Mindshare, undated (Removed to Subsidiaries and Related Firms, Restricted Materials, box SR6)] (Box SR5)
  - National Television Association (New York, N.Y.), 1991
    - Viewers' Choice: The Value of Higher Ratings, 1991 (Box SR5)
  - PACT (New York, N.Y.), 1982
    - Positioning Advertising Copy Testing, 1982 (Box SR5)
  - Simmons Market Research Bureau--SMRB (New York, N.Y.), 1980-1985
    - 1980 Study of Media and Markets, 1980 (Box SR5)
    - 1982 Study of Media and Markets, 1982 (Box SR5)
    - 1984 Study of Media and Markets, 1984 (Box SR5)
    - Audience Measurement Procedures, 1978 (Box SR5)
    - Choices, 1987 (Box SR5)
    - Cluster Plus Marketing, 1983 (Box SR5)
    - College Market, 1983 (Box SR5)
    - Dependable Data for Advertising and Marketing Decisions, 1985 (Box SR5)
    - Major Market Index Plan, 1978 (Box SR5)
    - Product Information Booklet, 1984 (Box SR5)
    - Simmons, circa 1984 (Box SR5)
    - Simmons-Scarborough Pamphlet, 1985 (Box SR5)
    - Simmons Study of Media and Markets, 1983 (Box SR5)
    - Simmons Teenage Research Study, 1984 (Box SR5)
    - Study of Media and Markets RPC Levels, 1984 (Box SR5)
    - Subscriber Lists, 1984-1985 (Box SR5)
    - Xpedite!, 1985 (Box SR5)
  - Society of Illustrators, 1992
    - Catalog, 1992 (Box SR5)
  - Soskin/Thompson Associates (New York, N.Y.), 1980
    - Direct Response to the 1980s, circa 1980 (Box SR5)
  - Thompson Recruitment Advertising, 1993
    - [ How Are We Feeling Today?, 1993 (Removed to Subsidiaries and Related Firms, Restricted Materials, box SR6)] (Box SR5)
  - Tihama (Jedda, Saudi Arabia), 1980s
    - Tihama (in Arabic), circa 1980s (Box SR5)
  - Tyton Information Service (London), undated
    - Marketing to Consumers, undated (Box SR5)
  - Subsidiaries and Related Firms, Restricted Materials (Closed to non-JWT users), 1994-2000 and undated
    - Contract Advertising Limited (Box SR6)
      - Up Front, vol. 3, 1995 (Box SR6)
      - Upbeat, 1994 (Box SR6)
    - JWT Specialized Communications, Inc.
      - Escape the Mundane, 2000 (Box SR6)
      - JWT Specialized Communications, circa 1996 (Box SR6)
    - JWT Works
      - Working Wire, 2000 (Box SR6)
    - JWT Worldwide
      - Cold Hard Facts, 1995, undated, 2 folders (Box SR6)
    - Mindshare
      - Making the Partnership Work, 1999 (Box SR6)
      - Some Things We Learned About Launching Mindshare, undated (Box SR6)
- Oversize Materials, 7 boxes
  - Domestic Publications--General, 1933-2005
    - 1933 (Box OV1)
      - Competition under NRA (Box OV1)
    - Circa 1940
      - Development and Application of Ideas in Advertising (Box OV1)
    - 1954
      - Successful Examples of Mass Education by Clients of J. Walter Thompson Co. (Box OV1)
    - 1961
      - Introducing the J. Walter Thompson Co. to Pittsburgh (Box OV1)
    - 1964
      - Lidov Mural (Box OV1)
    - Circa 1966
      - Inside this Booklet You'll Find 8 Ads... (Box OV1)
    - 1980
      - Advertising Chicago Style: A Character All Its Own (Box OV1)
    - 1984
      - Thompson (Box OV1)
    - 1986
      - 1986 JWT/FDAF Meeting, August 10-13 (Box OV1)
    - 1989
      - Advertising Leadership 1864-1989 (Box OV1)
    - 1994 (Box OV1A)
      - Power of the Old, Shock of the New (JWT San Francisco) (Box OV1A)
    - 2002-2003 (Box OV2)
      - Passion: North America, 2 folders (Box OV2)
    - 2005
      - Hold My Skateboard While I Kiss Your Girlfriend (Box OV2)